Art and Architecture of China Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- Painting (Box 7)
  - Yüan dynasty, 1260-1368 (Box 14)
    - Known Artists (Box 15)
      - Kao K'o-Kung, 1248-1310 (Box 16)
        - Cities (Box 16)
          - Shanghai (Box 16)
          - Taipei (Box 16)
            - Various Titles (Box 16)
            - Clearing Weather in the Spring Mountains (Box 16)
            - Rain in the Summer Mountains (Box 16)
            - Verdant Peaks above the Grounds (Box 16)
            - White Clouds & Green Mountains (Box 16)
      - K'o Chiu-Ssu, 1290-1343 (Box 16)
      - Ko Yung-T'ien (Box 16)
      - Ku An, ac. c. 1330 (Box 16)
      - Ku Te-Hui, 1310-1369 (Box 16)
      - Kuan Tao-Sheng, 1262-1319 (Box 16)
      - Kung Su-Jan, late 12th century (Box 16)
      - Kuo Pi, 1280-1335 (Box 16)
      - Li K'an, 1245-1320 (Box 16)
        - Various Titles (Box 16)
        - Cities (Box 16)
          - Indianapolis (Box 16)
          - Kansas City (Box 16)
          - Nanking [Slide box 94] (Box 16)
          - New York (Box 16)
      - Li Sheng (Box 16)
      - Li Shih-Hsing, 1282-1328 (Box 16)
        - Various Titles (Box 16)
        - Cities (Box 16)
          - Cleveland (Box 16)
      - Li Yao-Fu, ac.c. 1300 (Box 16)
      - Li Yung-Chin (Box 16)
      - Lin Chuan-A (Box 16)
      - Liu Kuan-Tao, ac.c. 1270-1300 (Box 16)
      - Liu Shan-Chou (Box 16)
      - Liu Yin, 1249-1293 (Box 16)
      - Liu Yuan, 1279-1368 (Box 16)
      - Lo Chih-Ch'üan, c. 1300 (Box 16)
        - Various Titles (Box 16)
        - Cities (Box 16)
          - Cleveland (Box 16)
          - New York (Box 16)
      - Lu Kuang, ac.c. 1325 (Box 16)
      - Ma Wan, ac. 1325-1365 (Box 16)
      - Meng Yü-Chien [Slide box 95] (Box 16)
      - Nan Chuang Chu-Sou, ac. 14th century (Box 16)
      - Ni Tsan, 1301-1374 (Box 16)
        - Various Titles (Box 16)
        - Cities (Box 16)
          - Cleveland (Box 16)
            - Bamboo, Rock & Tall Tree (Box 16)
          - New York (Box 16)
            - Various Titles (Box 16)
            - Woods & Valleys of Yu-Shan (Box 16)
          - Peking (Box 16)
          - Shanghai (Box 16)
            - Various Titles (Box 16)
            - Autumn Clearing over River Lodge (Box 16)
          - Taipei (Box 16)
            - Various Titles [Slide boxes 95-96] (Box 16)
            - Bamboo, Rock & Old Tree [Slide box 96] (Box 16)
            - Empty Groves after the Rain (Box 16)
            - Jung-Hsi Studio (Box 16)
            - Lodge on the River Bank (Box 16)
            - Mountain Scenery with River Lodge (Box 16)
      - P'u-Ming, ac. c. 1340-1350 (Box 16)
      - Ren Renfa, 1255-1328 (Box 16)
        Xx Jen Jen-Fa
      - Shang Ch'i, ac. c. 1295-1345 (Box 16)
      - Sheng Ch'ang-Nien (Box 16)
      - Sheng Chu, ac. 14th century (Box 16)
      - Sheng Mou, 1313-1362 (Box 16)
        - Various Titles (Box 16)
        - Cities (Box 16)
          - Cleveland (Box 16)
          - Nanking (Box 16)
          - Taipei (Taichung) (Box 16)
            - Various Titles (Box 16)
            - Boating in Autumn (Box 16)
      - Sun Chün-Tse [Slide box 97] (Box 17)
      - Tan Chih-Jui, c. 14th century (Box 17)
      - T'ang Ti, 1296-1364 (Box 17)
        - Cities (Box 17)
          - New York (Box 17)
          - Shanghai (Box 17)
          - Taipei (Taichung) (Box 17)
      - Teng Tzu-Fang, 14th century (Box 17)
      - Ting Ye-Fu (Box 17)
      - Ts'ai Shan (Box 17)
      - Ts'ao Chih-Po, 1272-1355 (Box 17)
        - Various Titles (Box 17)
        - Cities (Box 17)
          - Peking (Box 17)
          - Princeton (Box 17)
          - Taipei (Box 17)
            - Various Titles (Box 17)
            - Clearing after Snow on the Mountain Peaks (Box 17)
            - Twin Pines (Box 17)
      - Tsou Fu-Lei, c. 14th century (Box 17)
      - Wang Chen-p'eng, c. 1280-1329 (Box 17)
        - Various Titles (Box 17)
        - Cities (Box 17)
          - Indianapolis (Box 17)
          - New York (Box 17)
            - Dragon Boat Regatta on the Chin-Ming Lake (Box 17)
            - Vimalakirti and the Single Doctrine [Slide box 98] (Box 17)
          - Peking (Box 17)
          - Taipei (Taichung) (Box 17)
      - Wang Meng, ac. 1308-1385 (Box 17)
        - Various Titles (Box 17)
        - Cities (Box 17)
          - Cleveland (Box 17)
          - New York (Box 17)
          - Peking (Box 17)
          - Shanghai (Box 17)
            - Various Titles (Box 17)
            - Dwelling in the Ch'ing-Pien Mountains (Box 17)
            - Spring Mountains (Box 17)
          - Suchow [Slide box 99] (Box 17)
          - Taipei (Taichung) (Box 17)
            - Various Titles (Box 17)
            - Autumn Groves & Ten-Thousand Valleys (Box 17)
            - Retreat at Chü-Chü (Box 17)
            - Stream & Mountain Recluse (Box 17)
            - Thatched Lodge in Autumn Hills (Box 17)
      - Wang Mien, 1287-1359 (Box 17)
      - Wang Yüan, c. 1350 (Box 17)
        - Various Titles (Box 17)
        - Cities (Box 17)
          - Cleveland (Box 17)
          - Peking (Box 17)
          - Shanghai (Box 17)
      - Wei Chiu-Ting, ac. 1350-1370 (Box 17)
      - Wen Jih-Kuan, ac. late 13th century (Box 17)
      - Wu Chen, 1280-1354 (Box 17)
        - Various Titles (Box 17)
        - Cities (Box 17)
          - Cleveland (Box 17)
          - Peking [Slide box 100] (Box 17)
          - Shanghai (Box 17)
            - Fishermen (Box 17)
          - Taipei (Taichung) (Box 17)
            - Various Titles (Box 17)
            - Bamboo Album (Box 17)
            - Mountain among Mountains (Box 17)
            - The Old Fisherman (Box 17)
            - Spring Morning on the River (Box 17)
            - Two Junipers (Box 17)
          - Washington (Box 17)
      - Wu-Chu-Tzu [Slide box 101] (Box 17)
      - Wu T'ai-Su (Box 17)
      - Wu T'ing-Hui (Box 17)
      - Yao T'ing-Mei, ac. 14th century (Box 17)
      - Yao Yen-Ch'ing, 14th century (Box 17)
      - Yen Hui, 14th century (Box 17)
        - Various Titles (Box 17)
        - Cities (Box 17)
          - Cleveland (Box 17)
            - Various Titles (Box 17)
            - Lantern Night Excursion of Chung (Box 17)
      - Yen Keng, ac. c. 1300 (Box 17)
      - Yin T'o-Lo (Box 17)
      - Zhang Yu, 1238-1350 (Box 17)
  - Ming dynasty, 1368-1644 (Box 17)
    - Artist Unknown (Box 17)
      - Various Titles (Box 17)
      - Cleveland (Box 17)
      - Kansas City (Box 17)
        - Various Titles (Box 17)
        - Deer [Slide box 102] (Box 17)
        - Gathering the Peaches of Immortality (Box 17)
        - Meeting Friends in the Mountains (Box 17)
      - Nanking (Box 17)
      - New York (Box 17)
        - Various Titles (Box 17)
        - Eighteen Songs of a Nomad Flute (Box 17)
      - Peking (Box 17)
        - Various Titles (Box 17)
        - Emperor Hsuan-Tsung's Palace Am (Box 17)
      - Taipei (Taichung) (Box 17)
        - Various Titles (Box 17)
        - Copy of Gathering in the Western Garden (Box 17)
        - Snow Peaks [Slide box 103] (Box 17)
      - Washington (Box 17)
        - Various Titles (Box 17)
        - Cleaning out a Mountain Forest (Box 17)
    - Known Artists (Box 17)
      - Bian Jingzhao (Bian Wenjin), ac. c. 1426-1435 (Box 17)
        Filed under Pien Wenjin
      - Chan Chung-Ho (Box 17)
      - Chang Feng, ac. c. 1645-1673 (Box 17)
        - Various Titles (Box 17)
        - Cities (Box 17)
          - New York (Box 17)
      - Chang Fu (Box 17)
      - Chang Fu-Yang (Box 17)
      - Chang Hung (Box 17)
        - Various Titles (Box 17)
        - Cities (Box 17)
          - Taipei (Taichung) (Box 17)
            - Various Titles (Box 17)
            - Mt. Shih-Hsien (Box 17)
          - Zurich [Slide box 104] (Box 18)
            - Ling-Yen Mountain & Temple in the Snow (Box 18)
      - Chang Jui-T'u, 1576-1641 (Box 18)
      - Chang Ling, c. 1470-1520 (Box 18)
      - Chang Lu, 1464-1538 (Box 18)
        - Various Titles (Box 18)
        - Cities (Box 18)
          - Ching Yuan Chai Collection (Box 18)
          - Kamakura (Box 18)
          - Peking (Box 18)
          - Princeton (Box 18)
      - Chang Meng-K'uei, 16th century (Box 18)
      - Chang P'eng (Box 18)
      - Chao Ch'i (Box 18)
      - Chao Tso (Box 18)
      - Ch'en Ch'uan, 17th century (Box 18)
      - Ch'en Hsien-Chang, 1428-1500 (Box 18)
      - Ch'en Hung-Shou, 1599-1652 (Box 18)
        - Various Titles [Slide boxes 104-105] (Box 18)
        - Cities [Slide box 105] (Box 18)
          - Cleveland (Box 18)
            - Various Titles (Box 18)
            - Album of Paintings after Ancient Masters (Box 18)
          - Honolulu (Box 18)
            - Various Titles (Box 18)
            - Episodes in the Life of T'ao Ch'ien (Box 18)
          - New York (Box 18)
          - Peking (Box 18)
          - Shanghai (Box 18)
            - Various Titles (Box 18)
            - Lotus (Box 18)
          - Suchow (Box 18)
            - Album [Slide boxes 105-106] (Box 18)
          - Taipei [Slide box 106] (Box 18)
            - Various Titles (Box 18)
            - Assorted Paintings (Box 18)
            - Immortality under Pine (Box 18)
            - Sixteen Scenes from a Hermit's Life (Box 18)
          - Washington (Box 18)
          - Zurich (Box 18)
      - Ch'en Kua, ac. c. 1550-1554 (Box 18)
      - Chen Lu (Chen Xiangzhang), ac. c. 1440 (Box 18)
        Filed under Ch'en Hsien-Chang
      - Ch'en Shun, 1483-1544 (Box 18)
        - Various Titles (Box 18)
        - Cities (Box 18)
          - Ching Yuan Chai Collection (Box 18)
          - Cleveland (Box 18)
            - Looking for a Monastery in Misty Mountains (Box 18)
          - Honolulu (Box 18)
          - Kansas City (Box 18)
            - Various Titles (Box 18)
            - Lotus [Slide box 107] (Box 18)
          - New York (Box 18)
          - Taipei (Taichung) (Box 18)
      - Ch'en Tsung-Yuan (Box 18)
      - Ch'en Tzu-Ho (Box 18)
      - Chen Yuan (Box 18)
        Filed under Ch'en Tsung-Yuan
      - Emperor Ch'eng-Hua (Box 18)
      - Cheng Shih (Box 18)
      - Cheng Wen-Lin, ac. c. 16th century (Box 18)
      - Cheng Wen-Ying (Box 18)
      - Chi Chen, 15th century (Box 18)
      - Ch'iang Ch'ien (Box 18)
      - Chiang Kuei (Box 18)
      - Chiang Sung, 16th century (Box 18)
      - Ch'ien Ku, 1508-after 1574 (Box 18)
        - Various Titles (Box 18)
        - Fisherman's Joy [Slide box 108] (Box 18)
      - Ch'iu Shih, ac. c. 1550 (Box 18)
      - Ch'iu Ying (Box 18)
        - Various Titles (Box 18)
        - Cities (Box 18)
          - Cleveland (Box 18)
          - Hong Kong (Box 18)
            - Spring Dragon Emerges from Hibernation (Box 18)
          - Kansas City (Box 18)
            - Farewell at Hsun-Yang (Box 18)
          - Liaoning (Box 18)
          - Peking (Box 18)
          - Taipei (Taichung) (Box 18)
            - Various Titles (Box 18)
            - Conversation under Firmiana Trees (Box 18)
            - Landscapes after Sung & Yuan Masters (Box 18)
            - Late Return from a Spring Outing (Box 18)
            - Listening to Music (Box 18)
            - Palaces in the Mountains of the Immortals [Slide box 109] (Box 19)
            - Spring Dawn at the Palaces of Han (Box 19)
            - Testing the Water at the Pine Pavilion (Box 19)
            - Waiting for the Ferry in Autumn (Box 19)
          - Washington (Box 19)
            - Various Titles (Box 19)
            - Illustrations of Traditional Texts Written by Six (Box 19)
            - Ming Dynasty Calligraphers (Box 19)
      - Cho Ti (Box 19)
      - Chou Ch'en, ac. 1500-1535 (Box 19)
        - Various Titles (Box 19)
        - Cities (Box 19)
          - Cleveland (Box 19)
            - Beggars & Street Characters (Box 19)
          - Honolulu (Box 19)
            - Street Characters (Box 19)
          - Kansas City [Slide box 110] (Box 19)
            - Various Titles (Box 19)
            - The North Sea (Box 19)
          - Nanking (Box 19)
          - Peking (Box 19)
          - Taipei (Taichung) (Box 19)
            - Various Titles (Box 19)
            - Chess at the Pine Window (Box 19)
      - Chou Chih-Mien, ac. c. 1580-1610 (Box 19)
      - Chou Ch'uan, 15th century (Box 19)
      - Chou T'ien-Ch'iu, 1514-1595 (Box 19)
      - Chou Wei (Box 19)
      - Chou Wen-Ching, ac. c. 1430-1460 (Box 19)
      - Chü Chieh, 16th century (Box 19)
      - Chu Fei (Box 19)
      - Chü Mou-Shih (Box 19)
      - Chu Pang (Box 19)
      - Chu Tuan, ac. c. 1505-1525 (Box 19)
      - Chung Li, c. 1460-1500 (Box 19)
      - Cui Zizhong, ?-1644 (Box 19)
        Filed under Ts'ui Tzu-Chung
      - Dai Jin, 1388-1462 (Box 19)
        Filed under Tai Chin
      - Ding Yunpeng, 1547-1621 (Box 19)
        Filed under Ting Yun-P'eng
      - Du Dacheng (Box 19)
        Filed under Tu Ta-Ch'eng
      - Du Jin, ac. c. 1465-1487 (Box 19)
        Filed under Tu Chin
      - Du Qiong, 1396-1474 (Box 19)
        Filed under Tu Ch'iung
      - Gu Ningyuan, ac. c. 1636 (Box 19)
        Filed under Ku Ning-Yuan
      - Guan Si, ac. c. 1590-1630 (Box 19)
        Filed under Kuan Ssu
      - Guo Chun, 1370-1444 (Box 19)
        Filed under Kuo Ch'un
      - Guo Xu, 1456-after 1526 (Box 19)
        Filed under Kuo Hsu
      - Ho Ch'eng, ac. early 15th century (Box 19)
      - Hou Mou-Kung, ac. late 16th century (Box 19)
      - Hsia Chang, 1388-1470 [Slide box 111] (Box 19)
        - Various Titles (Box 19)
        - Cities (Box 19)
          - Peking (Box 19)
          - Shanghai (Box 19)
          - Taipei (Taichung) (Box 19)
      - Hsia Chih, 15th century (Box 19)
      - Hsia K'uei, 15th century (Box 19)
      - Hsia Shen (Box 19)
      - Hsiang Sheng-Mo, 1597-1658 (Box 19)
        - Cities (Box 19)
          - Various Titles (Box 19)
          - Cleveland (Box 19)
          - Zurich (Box 19)
      - Hsiang Te-Hsin (Box 19)
      - Hsiang Yüan-Pien, 1525-1590 (Box 19)
      - Hsieh Chin, ac. 15th century (Box 19)
      - Hsieh Huan, c. 1368-1435 (Box 19)
      - Hsieh Shih-Ch'en, 1487-after 1567 (Box 19)
        - Various Titles (Box 19)
        - Cities (Box 19)
          - Cleveland (Box 19)
          - Honolulu [Slide box 112] (Box 19)
          - Peking (Box 19)
          - Taipei (Taichung) (Box 19)
      - Hsien Tsung, 1448-1487 (Box 19)
      - Hsu Ching, 15th century (Box 19)
      - Hsu I, ac. 1640 (Box 19)
      - Hsu Lin, ac. c. 1510-1550 (Box 19)
      - Hsu Pen, 1345-1397 (Box 19)
        - Various Titles (Box 19)
        - Cities (Box 19)
          - Cleveland (Box 19)
      - Hsu Wei, 1521-1593 (Box 19)
        - Various Titles (Box 19)
        - Cities (Box 19)
          - Honolulu (Box 19)
            - Twelve Plants (Box 19)
          - Peking (Box 19)
          - Suchow [Slide box 113] (Box 19)
          - Stockholm (Box 19)
      - Hsüan Tsung, 1398-1435 (Box 19)
      - Hsueh Wu, 1564-c. 1637 (Box 19)
      - Hu Ts'ung (Box 19)
      - Huang Chi (Box 19)
      - Huang Tao-Chou, 1585-1646 (Box 19)
      - Jiang Song, ac. c. 1500 (Box 19)
        Filed under Chiang Sung
      - Ju Jie, ?-1585 (Box 19)
        Filed under Chu Chieh
      - Ju Moshi, ac. c. 1600 (Box 19)
        Filed under Chu Mou-Shih
      - Ku I-Te, first half of 17th century (Box 19)
      - Ku Ning-Yuan, ac. c. 1636 (Box 19)
      - Kuan Ssu, ac. c. 1590-1630 (Box 19)
      - Kuo Ch'un (Box 19)
      - Kuo Hsü, 1456-1526 (Box 19)
      - Lan Ying, 1585-1665 (Box 19)
        - Various Titles (Box 19)
        - Cities (Box 19)
          - Landscapes after Sung & Yüan Masters (Box 19)
          - Honolulu [Slide box 114] (Box 19)
            - Album of Landscapes (Box 19)
          - Peking (Box 19)
          - Taipei (Taichung) (Box 19)
            - Various Titles (Box 19)
            - Landscapes after Old Masters, 1635 (Box 19)
      - Li Chen, 1570-after 1640 (Box 19)
      - Li Chu (Box 19)
      - Li Liu-Fang, 1575-1629 (Box 19)
      - Li Ma-Tou, 1552-1610 (Box 19)
      - Li Shih-Ta, ac. c. 1573-1619 (Box 19)
      - Li Tsai, 15th century (Box 19)
        - Cities (Box 19)
          - Various Titles (Box 19)
          - Liaoning (Box 19)
            - Life of T'ao Yuan-Ming (Box 19)
      - Lin Liang, ac. c. 1485-1505 [Slide box 115] (Box 20)
        - Cities (Box 20)
          - Various Titles (Box 20)
          - New York (Box 20)
          - Peking (Box 20)
          - Princeton (Box 20)
      - Liu Chieh (Box 20)
      - Liu Chung-Hsien (Box 20)
      - Liu Chüeh, 1410-1472 (Box 20)
      - Liu Chün, ac. 1400-1450 (Box 20)
      - Liu Shih-Ju, 16th century (Box 20)
      - Liu Tu (Box 20)
      - Liu Yuan-Ch'I, ac. c. 1620-1633 (Box 20)
      - Lu Ch'ao-Yang, 15th century (Box 20)
      - Lu Chi, ac. 1488-1505 [Slide boxes 115-116] (Box 20)
      - Lu Chih, 1496-1576 [Slide box 116] (Box 20)
        - Cities (Box 20)
          - Honolulu (Box 20)
          - Suchow (Box 20)
          - Taipei (Taichung) (Box 20)
          - Washington (Box 20)
      - Lu Ching-Fu (Box 20)
      - Lu Shih-Tao, c. 1510-1570 (Box 20)
      - Lu T'ang (Box 20)
      - Lu Wen-Ying, c. 1500 (Box 20)
      - Ma Chun (Box 20)
      - Ma Shih, 15th century [Slide box 117] (Box 20)
      - Mi Wan-Chung, ac. 1617-1628 (Box 20)
      - Miu Fu (Box 20)
      - Mo Shih-Lung (Box 20)
        - Various Titles (Box 20)
        - Cities (Box 20)
          - Nanking (Box 20)
      - Mou I (Box 20)
      - Ni Tuan (Box 20)
      - Ni Yuan-Lu, 1593-1644 (Box 20)
      - Pien Wen-Chin, ac. 1413-1435 (Box 20)
        - Various Titles (Box 20)
        - Cities (Box 20)
          - Taipei (Taichung) (Box 20)
            - Flowers & Birds (Box 20)
            - Three Friends & The Hundred Birds (Box 20)
      - Pien Wen-Yu, 1611-1671 (Box 20)
      - P'u-Ho, 1593-1683 (Box 20)
      - Qian Gu, 1508-after 1574 (Box 20)
        Filed under Ch'ien Ku
      - Qiu Ying, ac. c. 1500-1525 (Box 20)
        Filed under Ch'iu Ying
      - Qiu Zhu (Qiu Shi), ac. c. 1550 (Box 20)
        Filed under Ch'iu Shih
      - Shang Hsi, ac. c. 1430-1440 (Box 20)
      - Shao Mi, ac. c. 1620-1660 (Box 20)
        - Various Titles (Box 20)
        - Cities (Box 20)
          - Peking (Box 20)
          - Taipei (Taichung) (Box 20)
      - Shen Chen, 1400-after 1460 (Box 20)
      - Shen Chou, 1427-1509 (Box 20)
        - Various Titles [Slide boxes 117-118] (Box 20)
        - Private Collection [Slide box 118] (Box 20)
          - Various Titles (Box 20)
          - Landscape Album for Chou Wei-te (Box 20)
        - Cities (Box 20)
          - Boston (Box 20)
            - Various Titles (Box 20)
            - Album of Eight Landscapes & Poems (Box 20)
          - Cleveland (Box 20)
            - Acacia Tree & Chrysanthemums (Box 20)
            - Flowering Crabapple (Box 20)
            - Twelve Views of Tiger Hill [Slide box 119] (Box 20)
          - Honolulu (Box 20)
            - Various Titles (Box 20)
            - Birds & Tree (Box 20)
          - Kansas City (Box 20)
            - Various Titles (Box 20)
            - Landscape in Style of Ni Tsan (Box 20)
            - Traveling through the Famous Sights of Wu (Box 20)
          - Liaoning (Box 20)
            - Various Titles (Box 20)
            - Yen-chiang Tieh-chang (Box 20)
          - New York (Box 20)
          - Osaka (Box 20)
          - Peking (Box 20)
            - Various Titles (Box 20)
            - Album of Dream Journey [Slide box 120] (Box 20)
          - Suchow (Box 20)
            - Various Titles (Box 20)
            - Junipers (Box 20)
          - Taipei (Box 20)
            - Various Titles (Box 20)
            - Collection of Views of Wu (Box 20)
            - Landscapes (Album) [Slide box 121] (Box 21)
            - Landscapes in the Spirit of Ni Tsan (Box 21)
            - Lofty Mt. Lu (Box 21)
            - Paintings of the Essence (Box 21)
            - Studies of Flowers & Animals (Box 21)
            - Towering Mountains above Retreat (Box 21)
            - Walking with a Staff (Box 21)
          - Zurich (Box 21)
      - Shen Hao, 1586-after 1661 (Box 21)
      - Shen Heng, 1409-1477 (Box 21)
      - Shen Shih-Ch'en, ac.c. 1370-1400 (Box 21)
      - Shen Shih-Ch'ung, ac.c. 1611-1640 (Box 21)
        - Various Titles (Box 21)
        - Flowers (Box 21)
      - Shen Yu, 1377-1448 [Slide box 122] (Box 21)
      - Sheng Mao-Yeh, ac. 17th century (Box 21)
        - Various Titles (Box 21)
        - Landscapes (Box 21)
        - Landscapes Inspired by T'ang Poems (Box 21)
      - Shih Chung, 1437-1517 (Box 21)
      - Shih Jui, c. 1424-1435 (Box 21)
      - Shih Wen (Box 21)
      - Sun Chih, ac.c. 1550-1580 (Box 21)
      - Sun K'o-hung, 1532-1610 (Box 21)
      - Sun Lung (Box 21)
        - Various Titles (Box 21)
        - Paintings from Life (Box 21)
      - Sung Hsü, 1523-1605 (Box 21)
      - Sung K'o, 1327-1387 (Box 21)
      - Tai Chin, 1388-1462 [Slide box 123] (Box 21)
        - Various Titles (Box 21)
        - Cities (Box 21)
          - Hong Kong (Box 21)
          - Liaoning (Box 21)
          - Peking (Box 21)
          - Shanghai (Box 21)
          - Suchow (Box 21)
          - Taipei (Box 21)
            - Various Titles (Box 21)
            - Landscape [Slide box 124] (Box 21)
            - Returning Late from a Spring Outing (Box 21)
          - Washington (Box 21)
      - T'ang Yin, 1470-1524 (Box 21)
        - Various Titles (Box 21)
        - Cities (Box 21)
          - Honolulu (Box 21)
          - Nanking (Box 21)
          - New York (Box 21)
            - Various Titles (Box 21)
            - Landscape Album (Box 21)
          - Peking (Box 21)
            - Various Titles (Box 21)
            - Shih-ming t'u (Box 21)
          - Princeton (Box 21)
          - Shanghai (Box 21)
          - Suchow (Box 21)
          - Taipei (Box 21)
            - Various Titles [Slide boxes 124-125] (Box 21)
            - Clearing after Snow in a Mountain Pass [Slide box 125] (Box 21)
            - Farming in Chiang-Nan (Box 21)
            - Figures in T'ang Style (Box 21)
            - Landscapes & Figures (Box 21)
            - Late Spring in the Ravine (Box 21)
            - Parting from Chin-Ch'ang (Box 21)
            - Scholars (Box 21)
            - Secluded Fishermen on an Autumn River (Box 21)
            - T'ao Ku Presents a Poem (Box 21)
            - Watching the Ploughing (Box 21)
            - Whispering Pines on a Mountain Path (Box 21)
          - Washington (Box 21)
      - T'ao Ch'eng, ac.c. 1480-1532 (Box 21)
      - T'ao Hung (Box 21)
      - T'ien-Ju, 15th century (Box 21)
      - Ting Yu-Ch'uan, 15th century (Box 21)
      - Ting Yün-P'eng, ac.c. 1584-1638 [Slide box 126] (Box 21)
        - Cities (Box 21)
          - Various Titles (Box 21)
          - Honolulu (Box 21)
            - Various Titles (Box 21)
            - Arhat Scroll (Box 21)
          - Peking (Box 21)
          - Taipei (Box 21)
            - Various Titles (Box 21)
            - Washing the Elephant (Box 21)
            - White Horse Brings the Sutras (Box 21)
          - Zurich (Box 21)
      - Ts'ao Miao-Ching, c. mid-14th century (Box 21)
      - Tseng Ch'ing, 1568-1650 (Box 21)
      - Tsou Chih-Lin, ac.c. 1645 (Box 21)
      - Ts'ui Tzu-Chung, c. 1595-1644 (Box 21)
        - Cities (Box 21)
          - Various Titles (Box 21)
          - Taipei (Box 21)
            - Various Titles (Box 21)
            - Examining Antiques in the Shade of Wu-T'ung (Box 21)
      - Trees (Box 21)
      - Tu Chin, ac. 1465-1487 [Slide boxes 126-127] (Box 21–22)
      - Tu Ch'iung, 1396-1474 [Slide box 127] (Box 22)
        - Various Titles (Box 22)
        - Cities (Box 22)
          - Honolulu (Box 22)
            - Landscape (Box 22)
          - Taipei (Box 22)
      - Tu Ta-Ch'eng (Box 22)
      - Tung Ch'i-Ch'ang, 1555-1636 (Box 22)
        - Various Titles (Box 22)
        - Cities (Box 22)
          - Boston (Box 22)
          - Cleveland (Box 22)
            - Various Titles (Box 22)
            - Autumn Mountains (Box 22)